coupons.in 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of your personal information is important to us. Here is information on what type of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our site coupons.in, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

We collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Firefox or Internet Explorer), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site coupons.in.

**Email Address**

coupons.in is a free content web site. We do not require any information from you (not even a user name or password). We do not sell any information from our site to any third party. The only e-mail sent from our websites is in response to an inquiry that you may send us or as a result of joining our double opt-in e-mail list. If anything comes to your attention which could potentially be a violation of this policy, please let us know immediately so that we can investigate it and try to correct it.

**Privacy Policy of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information by coupons.in through your interaction with the web sites. Other web sites/merchants that may be accessible through links from our site coupons.in may have their own privacy policies and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. Our merchants and business partners may have their own privacy statements, too. We encourage you to verify the privacy statements provided by these other parties prior to providing them with information or taking advantage of an offer or promotion.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements to support our site coupons.in. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This Website uses Google for advertisements.
